/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data_c_1', {
    title: 'C.1 Prime Factorization',
    path: 'C.1-prime-factorization',
    children: [{
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 143}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{11}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{13}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 143}',
                answer: '\\primefac{143}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    },{
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 22}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{11}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 22}',
                answer: '\\primefac{22}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    },{
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 177}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{3}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{59}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 177}',
                answer: '\\primefac{177}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 105}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{3}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{5}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{7}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 105}',
                answer: '\\primefac{105}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 165}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{3}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{5}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{11}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 165}',
                answer: '\\primefac{165}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 1331}',
                answer: '\\exp{\\input{11}}{\\input{3}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 1331}',
                answer: '\\primefac{1331}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 200}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\exp{\\input{2}}{\\input{3}}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{5}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 200}',
                answer: '\\primefac{200}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 539}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\exp{\\input{7}}{\\input{2}}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{11}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 539}',
                answer: '\\primefac{539}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 63}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\exp{\\input{3}}{\\input{2}}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{7}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 63}',
                answer: '\\primefac{63}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 375}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{3}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{5}}{\\input{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 375}',
                answer: '\\primefac{375}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
